Maravil Thirivu Sookshikkuka is a thriller film directed by J Sasikumar.
A place near a hillside where vehicles which are
coming is meeting with accident..
a writer arrives and try to solve the mystery
Jayadevan, played by Prem Nazir.
Kaduva Kurien, played by Adoor Bhasi.
K. B. Menon, played by Thikkurissy Sukumaran Nair.
Puncture Antony, played by Bahadoor.
Chinnamma, played by Jayamalini.
Maravil Thirivu Sookshikkuka is a 1972 Indian
Malayalam-language crime thriller film, directed by J.
Sasikumar and produced by R.
The film stars Prem Nazir, Vijayasree, Adoor Bhasi
and Thikkurissy Sukumaran Nair.
The film had musical score by G.
The tone is intense.